ipodnn.com 2016-06-08

# Privacy Policy | MacNN

## Reviews

## Most Popular

## Most Discussed

© 2016 MNM Media LLC.. Privacy Policy is applicable to you. All rights reserved.

**MacNN.com Privacy Policy**  
Version 1.3

Internet user privacy is of paramount importance to MacNN.com and its related sites. The success of our business depends upon our ability to maintain the trust of our users. Below is information regarding MacNN's commitment to protect the privacy of users and to ensure the integrity of the Internet.

**User Information**

During your visit to the site, MacNN does not collect any personally-identifiable information about you beyond what you specifically volunteer. This information may be volunteered when you create an account through the MacNN discussion forums or article comment system. However, even then, MacNN does not use that stored information for any purpose other than to allow you to log in and post messages.

MacNN does, however, automatically collect certain non-personally-identifiable information about you, such as your browser type and the IP address that your ISP designates to your machine (which, usually changes periodically depending of your type of Internet connection). This is standard practice for web sites, and is not used for any purpose other than to statistically evaluate how we can design the site to best serve your needs. This information is not sold to any third parties or available to anybody outside of the MacNN staff.

**Cookies**

Along with countless other Web sites, MacNN uses cookies to enhance your experience. Cookies are used in the MacNN discussion forums to keep track of which messages have been posted since your last visit, easing the navigation of the forums. Cookies can also store your user name and password so that you do not have to log in each time you want to post a message or article comment, though you must specifically request that this feature be turned on. Other user settings such as preferred site display options are also managed by cookies.

Cookie data is not stored on the server, and therefore, not available for viewing by MacNN staff or any third parties. However, it is possible that security flaws exist in some browsers that would allow other site administrators to write malicious scripts that would collect this data without MacNN's knowledge, though this is quite unlikely.

**Third-party Ad Server**

A portion of the advertisements displayed on the MacNN Network are served by third-party advertisement providers, including Advertising.com, TribalFusion, Google, and Federated Media. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

If you would like to opt-out of Non Personally Identifiable Information (PII) cookie tracking, please visit the NAI opt-out page here: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>.

We are committed to continuing to protect the privacy of our readers. If you have any additional questions, please contact us at Privacy@macnn.com.

We recommend that you review this Privacy Statement periodically, as MacNN may update it from time to time without notice to its users.

## Now AAPL Stock: 99.03 ( + 0.4 )

As reported following the second $1B Australian bond offering, Apple has issued an unusual 30-year US dollar bond in Taiwan, which raised between $1 billion and $1.2 billion, according to estimates. The yield on the bond was between 4.2 and 4.3 percent, much lower than comparable bond offerings from other large companies. Apple uses the bonds to raise money for its US operations, including stock buybacks and dividend distribution, since most of its profits come from foreign sales it cannot "repatriate" to the US without paying a second, and much higher, tax rate on the profits than it paid in the countries it uses for foreign headquarters. <http://bit.ly/1PgSSqk>

Apple's landing page for the live stream of its WWDC keynote, broadcast live from the Bill Graham Civic Auditorium in San Francisco on Monday June 13 at 10AM Pacific, is now live. While the keynote will be available to the public, most other events broadcast through the company's Apple TV channel (supported on second-generation and later) will be limited to those with developer accounts. The keynote, which uses HTTP Live Streaming technology, can also be accessed on iOS devices running iOS 7 or higher, Macs using Safari 6.0.5 or later, and on Windows PCs using Microsoft Edge for Windows 1.0. <http://apple.co/1tfOrbi>

The standalone iOS app for free educational service iTunes U has been updated to add support for storing and retrieving documents from various cloud services, ranging from Apple's own iCloud to third-party ones such as Google Drive, Dropbox, and Box. Users must simply have an existing account with the various services, and have the mobile app version of the service installed and signed in. The update also allows the importing of managed class rosters from Apple School Manager, and the ability to use Notability and Explain Everything project files as course materials or hand-ins from students. The update is available on the iOS App Store.[ [42.0MB] ](https://geo.itunes.apple.com/us/app/itunes-u/id490217893?mt=8) []()

Internet and cable TV provider Comcast has announced a new Xfinity gigabit-speed service for residents and businesses in Nashville, Tennessee, in reaction to municipal community-owned and Google Fiber ISP competition. Customers willing to commit to a three-year contract will see 1Gbps down and 35Mbps up, with no data cap, for $70 per month, though the month-by-month price is a significantly more expensive deal: $140 per month, with a 1TB data cap. Comcast and AT&T have vigorously opposed municipal cable efforts like EPB in Chattanooga, which offers up to 1Gbps speeds for $70 per month without contracts. <http://bit.ly/1Uxwiex>

According to Swiss media reports, Apple Pay could be launching in Switzerland on the same day as the kickoff of Apple's Worldwide Developers Conference -- Monday, June 13. The reports could be a foreshadowing of major announcements at WWDC about Apple Pay expansion in Europe, where merchants are far better prepared for NFC payments of all types (both "contactless" physical cards, and mobile wallet systems) than in the US. The news comes on the heels of Canada's banks fully rolling out Apple Pay support last week. Thus far, the US, Canada, Australia, Singapore, and mainland China are the only countries fully supporting Apple Pay. <http://bit.ly/1UxuSkh>

The US International Trade Commission will investigate a complaint against Apple and AT&T brought by haptic technology company Immersion, alleging that Apple's smartphones and some laptops violate Immerision's patents through the use of Force Touch and 3D Touch. "The complaint ... alleges violations of section 337 of the Tariff Act of 1930 in the importation into the United States and sale of certain mobile and portable electronic devices incorporating haptics (including smartphones and laptops) and components thereof that infringe patents asserted by the complaint," the announcement says in part. Immersion is seeking a limited exclusion order, and "cease and desist" orders. <http://1.usa.gov/1UxqZff>

Fujitsu today unveiled ScanSnap Cloud, a new service that enables ScanSnap scanner customers to simply send data directly from their ScanSnap iX500 or iX100 scanners to popular cloud-based services such as Dropbox, Evernote, Expensify, Google, and OneDrive. Customers can simply set profiles for each category by selecting the cloud service of their choice in the free, dedicated app, and ScanSnap Cloud automatically sorts and delivers the data while delivering optimized scanned images with automatic paper-size and color detection, automatic page rotation and blank-page removal using 'Smart Naming' to name files using extracted keywords and dates from the scanned documents. It is now available for all new and current ScanSnap iX Series customers at www.ScanSnapCloud.com. <http://bit.ly/1UxqxgW>
